The End Narancia, when you get a sec,
let me see that key I risked my life for.
Huh? Here.
No, don't throw it!
Aaargh!
That hurt, dumbass!
You are such a drama queen.
I'd be happy my hand had feeling at
all given what you just went through.
The damn thing has only been
reattached for 30 minutes, you idiot!
So happy or not, it still hurts.
But enough about that.
You safeguarded my daughter's life,
and therefore you have my gratitude.
Go to Napoli Cinderella,
Benario 6, look for the turtle at
the water fountain, and use this key.
You are to take her to Venice by train.
Postscript says, directives will
cease once we have arrived in Venice.
What the hell are we supposed
to find at this water fountain?
Don't know, but the boss said there was
a way to travel under the enemy's radar.
It'll be risky but we have to trust him
speaking of the boss do you think he's?
Maybe already there I mean it kind of
sounds like it that doesn't concern us.
Our focus is on finishing
the mission there's a train
bound for France in ten minutes
that we don't want to miss.
Mista we alone looks like
we're in the clear for now.
Once we get to the
station though I bet the
place will be swarming
with rats ready to snitch.
I can't imagine what you must be
going through suddenly having a target
on your back because of an estranged
father it must be terrifying.
Oh I feel you fugo I've
been preoccupied by our
lively new friends too
if you know what I mean.
No that's not what I
Please, miss, you gotta forget Fugo!
He didn't mean to come off
as an over-eager horndog!
I know it seems like we hit
the brakes so my man here!
Could peek at those jaunty jiggle sacks?
but I give you my word that's not it!
Blame his weakness in the face of Fugo!
Just shut up, would ya?
I was bracing for impact,
and you're making it sound like
I was trying to cop a veal!
Just promise me whatever you
do, you won't tell the boss!
Thank you.
There he is.
It's Bucciarati.
I don't believe it.
The dumbass actually showed up
to the station in broad daylight.
He'll regret that.
Maybe the pressure he's under has
made logic give way to desperation.
Or perhaps the Stronzo thinks he's figured
out a way to throw us off the trail.
I'll still butcher him!
He killed Illuso and Formaggio!
He's dead! Hey, moron!
Cool it with this stupid
butcher crap, you hear me?
It's annoying as all hell. Huh?
Our squadra of mafiosi has
no need for talk like that.
Leave that drivel to the weaklings.
Our group has a peculiar way about us.
By the time primitive thoughts
like that enter our minds,
the enemy's already been butchered.
There's no need to
announce the inevitable.
Such words have never crossed my lips.
Pesci, you need to follow my example.
Prove that you're one of us.
You understand.
Well, do ya?
I do.
I got it, big bro.
Say butchered from now on
like the job's a done deal.
Prosciutto
Listen,
I'll head over on the
platform here pesci you
get on and head to the
front car from the inside!
On it
We'll corner him!
We need the boss's daughter alive?
Bucciarati it's getting close to
departure time something wrong.
This is the only water fountain
here I'm sure about that.
But there's no way this was
designed for this keyhole.
And look at this.
You don't even need a key to open it.
It's nothing more than an access hatch.
Bucciarati, what about the
lock on that fire hydrant?
This lock isn't a match either. Merda!
How can this be the right place
if the key won't fit anywhere?
This is maddening!
Should we pass on this train?
The train in 15 minutes is bound for Rome.
Not a chance.
The enemy probably knows we're
here and are headed to the station.
We can't stay longer than we have to.
Benario 6.
The turtle by the fountain.
If this isn't the spot, then where is it?
Damn it! What now?
The turtle.
Ah!
Huh?
Explain, Pesci.
What the hell are you doing here? Huh?
What are you doing here, big bro?
Where did Bucciarati run off to?
I know I saw him climb aboard
the train right before I did.
And there's no way in hell you didn't pass
by him as he was walking down the aisle.
Well, I'm right, aren't I?
You gotta believe me,
I didn't see nothing!
Not Bucciarati, his annoying friends,
that new guy, not even the
boss's twerp, none of them!
This little disappearing
act doesn't sit right.
The train's about to take off, big bro.
They've got to be sneaking
around the station somewhere.
They just gotta be.
They don't know who's after them,
so they're waiting to spot us
before hopping on a getaway train.
I'm positive I'm not imagining things.
There was something by
that water fountain.
He must have picked it up.
He grabbed something dark by the
fountain before jumping on the train.
Pesci, get on!
But why? Just do it!
I don't know how they're doing it,
but I have a hunch that Bucciarati and his
little yes-men are
hiding out on this train.
And you're basing all that on a hunch?
The boss must be offering those
clots some kind of assistance.
We're gonna have to move quickly now.
My hunch says this is the last chance
we're gonna have before we lose him.
Stop gawking and get on the train!
A three-and-a-half-hour train
ride separates Napoli from France.
But the midway point, Reimi, lies
but a mere one-and-a-half hours away.
Oh, man, now we're stuck
on the train. Shut up.
Pesci, there's a space under the door.
Something must be back here. But what?
Isn't that room for the
guy who drives the train?
You really think seven
people could hole up
in there without a single person noticing?
That's crazy.
Can't be too careful.
Why don't you unleash
Fisherman and find out?
Do it.
Fisherman!
Hmm.
Well, I'm not picking up on seven
assholes, but I do sense two.
Come to papa.
Merida, what a tight squeeze.
Only room for the engineer
no matter I know those
bastards are somewhere on
this train huh hey wait?
Just a second I only hooked one of
them what Gibbs I could have sworn I
heard two hearts thumping in there so
why'd my rod only managed to hook the
NG guy hey Pesci get off your ass
we're searching the train from top to
bottom we'll find him and rip those
cowards out from their hiding spot but!
You're staying put.
If Bucciarati's goons figure
out that we're here too,
you can bet they'll come
rushing in to stop the train.
I got you covered, big bro.
And don't forget about their cargo.
As long as the girl's with them, they
can't tear through the train on a whim.
They have to play it safe.
Which is what gives us the upper hand.
We'll snatch the girl and off those
clowns before we reach Reimi Termini!
The key wasn't made to
fit in a keyhole but
it fit perfectly in the
shell of this turtle.
Somehow that activated
the turtle's special
ability the key seems
to function as a portal.
To an alternate space
one where we can remain
sight unseen so the
turtle is a stand user?
Where am I?
Under a seat?
Shit!
This place is the bomb diggity!
This turtle's like a loungy spaceship!
At first, I thought this room
was some sort of illusion.
But it's a bonafide structure.
And all the furniture is real, too.
Even the drinks are cold.
Perhaps the boss is responsible
for these accommodations.
For the most part, turtles will
remain quiet and still in dark spaces.
In other words, we should be able
to travel to Venice without issue.
Hmm.
I guess hiding in here
would be pretty dumb, huh?
I wish my gut talked to me
the way that my big bros does.
Is Big Bro making this haze?
Did you really?
The thankful death!
Bro, you're really doing it?
And you're going to do
it to everybody on board?
We don't even know if
they're on this train.
Shouldn't we figure that
out before we start?
I told you, we're going
to be thorough about this.
They're here all right, I know it.
Besides, you're making
a fuss over nothing.
Planes from all over fall from the sky
every year and the world keeps spinning.
These jumps are getting off easy.
It's being stuck inside a
turtle has its drawbacks.
It's kind of muggy.
Hey, Narancia, you want a drink too?
Hope you're good with it being cold.
There's cola,
and mineral water, sparkling water,
and apple, orange, and pineapple juice.
Hey, are you listening to me at all?
Huh?
You say something, Mista?
I asked if you wanted something to drink.
Though you might want to
try getting some shut-eye.
You've seen better days there, man.
I'll keep an eye on the
ceiling while you rest.
Sounds like a plan.
I'm actually starting to
feel a little achy anyway.
My back and shoulders are killing me.
I think I'll cop a squat.
Something warm would sure
hit the spot right now.
But nothing too heavy.
For the last time, all we've
got in the fridge are cold ones.
Come on, is your brain shut
down when you talk to people?
In that case, banana it is. Yeah.
Oh, gardens like these
really soothe the soul.
Your stress just melts away.
Ah, so heavenly.
Man, oh man,
what I'd give to bask in
that Garden of Eden's warm
sunshine just daydreaming
about the good old days.
Rose, would you cut that shit out?
Nobody wants your nasty-ass
spit on the damn pages!
Huh?
You're saying I did what now?
There's no way! You're crazy!
You're, uh, drooling
pretty bad there, man.
That is so freaking nasty.
The heck is that? Hey!
Huh?
I was craving this
banana, but it's no good.
I mean, just look at it.
It's like a piece of old stale
beef jerky. That's funny.
You really had me going there.
Good on you, Narancia.
Don't scare me like that.
It almost looks like that thing coming
out of your mouth is a real tooth.
I appreciate the commitment, but I
think you're taking the bit too far.
Just what is that dangling thing made of?
You say something again, mister?
Speak louder.
Stop whispering, would you?
I can't hear what you're saying.
These ears don't seem to be
working as well as they used to.
Oh, and would you just
look at this banana?
It's falling apart.
I can't eat something
like that! How gross!
Disgusting!
It's old and rotten!
This darn fruit's foul!
What?
What's going on?
Didn't you hear me?
The fruit's gone bad!
Why do you look like a freaking grandpa?
Alright then, I suppose I'll lead
my example and speak up first!
Can you hear me now?
I couldn't eat this thing if
you stuffed it down my throat!
Just look!
Every time I try to
touch it, it falls apart.
See, it's way past its prime.
Bucciarati! Yes, I see.
A stand did this.
One of our enemies must be
somewhere aboard this train.
Huh? What the hell?
What's with all this gray stuff?
Hold on, did this tuft of
hair come out of my head?
What in the hell is happening?
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Or are we fighting now?
They're all geriatrics!
Mommy! Please!
Wake up! Mommy!
Mommy!
Mom! Please!
Who the hell is this guy?
Wait, I can't be.
No way. Is this...
No, no, no.
Is this all fucked me?
What the heck are we supposed to do?
So, this stand makes people older.
Did they figure us out?
Did the enemy find out
we're hiding in this turtle?
Stay calm, Mista.
If they had any idea about
our reptilian bunker,
they would have launched
a more direct assault.
They don't know where we are.
This is a desperate
attempt to root us out.
But one thing's for sure.
Our enemies definitely know we're
hiding somewhere on this train.
In order to track down Trish, they're
willing to take out every passenger aboard.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You're telling me this
train is careening down
the tracks chock-full of
seniors on Death's door?
Precisely.
They're desperate, so they'll
do whatever it takes to beat us.
And they won't even bat an eye.
We now only have two choices before us.
Choice one, we take Trish and
get the hell off this train.
Or we ignore the fact that we don't know
our attacker's range and hunt them down.
Number two it is if we want to escape with
Trish then we have to stop this train.
Jumping now is a death
wish assassination is my
thing my six bullets will
find the enemy and put him
six feet under that's right
you're our ace sadly we're
out of time our bodies are
aging at blinding speed
Bucciarati my hands
look now my skin and nails are peeling off
they're disintegrating
you're right Bucciarati if we
don't act ASAP we're screwed?
No, don't be rash mister.
It's too early to abandon ship What crazy
bullshit are you going on about now?
You have to listen to me.
We can't retreat.
No, what we can't do is waste time.
Mista, listen.
We're all ears, Jean. Go on.
A question for you.
Why do you think we're all aging
at different rates from Bucciarati?
The aging's hit me and Mista a lot less,
and Trisha's better off than us. But why?
You can just chalk it up
to good genes or something.
I'm out of here! Mista,
why do you think our attackers are attacking
everything on the train that moves?
They have to know they
could very easily end
up killing Trish in
their efforts to kill us.
The speed of the aging
has to be conditional.
I'll cut right to the chase here.
I think our body heat is key.
They can discern men from women
by the differences in temperature.
I once read that women have a
higher body fat percentage than men.
So as a result, their body temperature
tends to be a bit more stable.
Moreover, women's cells tend
to age slower than men's,
which is why they supposedly live longer.
Didn't you say earlier that
it was getting warm in here?
They're observing the changes
in our body temperatures,
and they're using that to
control the speed of our aging.
All you have to remember is
that men age faster than women.
It's a real nice theory
when you put it like that.
But why am I fine while you're a geezer?
You're saying I'm a chick or something?
No, that's not it.
Think about it.
Our body temperatures would
be cooler than theirs.
Both of us were sipping on cold drinks,
but Narancia wasn't.
Son of a bitch!
Giorno, your theory was spot on!
We're aging at a slower rate than the rest
of you because our bodies were cooler!
Time to start cooling.
Now grab some ice and start
rubbing out those wrinkles!
Wait, Mista!
You have to figure out a way
to take that ice with you!
This is all we got?
Remember, everything depends
on destroying our enemy.
Focus.
The ice will be imperative
in being able to defeat them.
You have to do the deed before your
stand in the ice disappear completely!
Just the driver.
Everyone else is gone.
It's hot as hell they really are
attacking everything in sight how awful
Wonder if the turtle's
aging too but don't they
live for like a bajillion
years or something
Guess he'll outlive us
all what a drag you're
gonna get me killed bro
i hope all this is worth
What is my reckless big bro gonna
do if I start getting old, too, huh?
Well, now, if I can get the air running,
that may just cool everyone down.
Then I might be able to
slow down that freaky aging.
Yes!
It looks like they took the bank!
How'd this frickin'
hook get under my skin?
This can't be the guy that's
trying to age us to death.
Which means.
There are two of them.
We're dealing with two users.
You understand me?
I don't give a damn about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I do.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I do. I do.
I do. I'm freaking.
Thank you.